Hi my name is Stuti Goyal I am currently
placed in ICICI Loma as a management
trainee under the profile of underwriter so
my work there is setting claims doing
the risk management work for the ICICI
and I will be joining in April and I am
a PGDM finance student with major
in finance and minor in business analytics
what specific aspects of FIIB
program help you secure your placement
at ICICI Loma some specific
programs like the revision of the
financial base and giving the deep knowledge of
what are the risk management aspects
and each profile of the financial weather
technical and weather basics given to me the
faculty in the college has help me secure this
role because in the interview as well they were asking very
basic questions that majorly
student do not grasp during the time of
the studies but in this college our faculty has tried that well that we even
grasp the
basic knowledge  And given and able to answer these questions how do you see
yourself
advancing ICICI Loba object
insurance innovation and customer service so
my profile there is strictly
technical and for the underwriter so by applying
all my technical knowledge that I have learned here
wether art studio and power bee I will be
enhancing my work there and
looking to grow there what kind of
faculty support did you receive that helped you
in securing a job faculties were very
supportive during that time even I can give you some example
in my interview I have done
the research analysis on the company
called Zomato and on the prior day aa zen sir was
teaching about Zomato and the up to date
knowledge about what it is doing currently
and that too in the interview also they ask
me the same question and I gave the same answer
to that and they were very  Impressive so I can say
teachers are giving us up to date
knowledge about everything and teaching us that is
required for the industry what is one
unique aspect of FIIB that
significantly added your professional growth there
is a chance for everybody initially when I
entered the college I had
stage fear and I was not that very
confident but because of many
participation in many club activities
and taking roles and responsibilities
my confidence has boosted to that level
that if I go on a stage then I can
present myself without any hesitation
and with full confidence what piece of
advice would you give to juniors looking for
replacement I would give a simple piece of
advice that do not take lot of worry just
focus on what the faculties are teaching and
love just with a free mind focus on small
things and big things as  Well just do not
stress if you are studying well and your
concentrating in classes everything will be done
and